James Prater

3406 Playground Road, Caruthersville, MO 63830

(573) 359-8044

Jrp5mh@umsystem.edu www.linkedin.com/in/james-prater/

OBJECTIVE

With 4 years of direct technological work experience and many technological literacy courses taken, I am searching for a position that will benefit from my expertise in computer and technological usage, problem solving, and critical thinking.

EDUCATION

Caruthersville High School, Caruthersville, MO, High School Diploma

- Salutatorian

Arkansas Northeastern College, Blytheville, AR, Certificate of General Studies

University of Missouri-Columbia, Columbia, MO, Currently Enrolled (Freshman)

KEY SKILLS -

Computer Literacy
Problem Solving
Critical Thinking
Guiding and Teaching Others
Use of Microsoft Word,
PowerPoint, and Excel

EXPERIENCE

2016 - 2020

Audio, Visual, and Recording Technician • Volunteer, *Head Technician* • Caruthersville First Baptist Church, MO

Controlled audio, visual, and recording equipment for First Baptist Church, controlling microphone and music volume as well as displaying essential information in text form for those with hearing impairments, and using audio/video recording equipment for those unable to attend.

COMMUNICATION

Efficient and versatile written and oral communication, including presentation, writing, explanation and teaching, guiding, speech giving, and more.

LEADERSHIP

Lead Audio/Visual/Recording Technician at *Caruthersville First Baptist Church* (2016-2020)

Leader of Caruthersville High School Marching and Concert Band Trumpet Section (2018-2020)

REFERENCES

[Available upon request.]